Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is one love. Let me show you how to
make it. It's going to be very similar
to my vanilla base. So, we're using
Fairlife milk, sweetener, salt, zen gum,
some vanilla bean paste, but then we're
taking a medium sized banana and then
just throwing that in in halves. Now,
you should probably blend this mixture
up prior to freezing, but I usually just
throw the bananas in whole, and the
creamy does a great job of mixing them
up. Either way, you're going to be
totally fine, so it's up to you. Now, we
can talk mixins. So, the first mixin is
going to be the chocolate chip hack.
This is something I created a few months
ago. All you have to do is melt some
chocolate down with some coconut oil and
then just pour it into a hole down the
center of your creamy, run it on the
mixing setting, and you have perfect
creamy chocolate chips that get
distributed throughout the entire brine.
And for the rest of the toppings, I just
crumble up a few graham crackers and
then topped it with some caramel syrup.
And as I always ask in this series,
comment which Ben & Jerry's flavor you
want me to recreate